all righty today C challenge black side
stealth no Scrambler bloodless and 15
minutes so it's
bloodless that's fine aside from that
we've got no Scrambler which means you
have to clear the entire ST which
shouldn't be too bad either but aside
from that we've got 15 minutes
which I mean we've got a lot more stuff
to do now so we should be able to do it
decently fast but if
we cyber I assume you're looping that
right then we'll loot this
camera and then afterwards I assume we
can actually just yeah we can put your
hands up absolutely nothing we'll back
them up and hopefully no one walks right
over here right now because that will be
really really
awkward so we'll grab a this guys
cyber's going to stand on top of the
container for absolutely no reason and
we'll leave this back in the container
and then now we got to find another two
Gods which there's one over there and
there's one over
there right then once that one
leaves you should
probably when is that you know what we
can go up here we can loot this camera
first proba we wait for that to happen I
mean might as well
right all right that guard's far enough
away we'll just knock you out over here
and we got a key card so that's actually
fantastic so we'll grab cyber disguise
and then afterwards we'll get right to
this or at least get right to actually
entering restrict the area cyber you
should probably go back up there I've
literally got a disguise for you it's
not that
complicated and I suppose you could
leave that guard
alone really just leave him alone it's
not that difficult and now we'll run
right by loot this
camera right then loot this camera why
are you there just go somewhere else you
know maybe slightly further away that
that would be nice
just saying I kind of can't put a gun
out right now
so cyber actually there is no camera
here you can just loot
that all right
then that guard's moving I'm taking this
opportunity I'm taking this
opportunity get down all of you and
cyber how did you get a radio over
there you know I'm slightly concerned
that all right cyber should be fine F
we'll back up the bodies over here and
we're going to hide them and we're going
to get right to the restricted area I
mean
in a significantly low amount of time
too which is really nice we're into the
restrict area in just over 2 minutes and
30 seconds so back this side we'll hide
this body and then afterwards we'll move
right in that door's open perfect C's
going to be able to get in here and now
all we got to do is it's turn not all
right there are two Gods walking down
the corridor that's for sure
why you put your hands up anyone else
perfect now that
was definitely not enjoyable but cybus
just answer two radios hopefully this
goes well I'm going to take that gun and
then afterwards we're going to knock out
this
guard so now we got to do now is B up
this body and leave that up over here
along with the gun because we're not
carrying an unpress i7 around for
absolutely no
reason I mean there is a you're walking
back over
here go on move
past or just stand
there I don't think there's a camera
over there so you know what we're going
to
do we're going to bag you up and then
we'll just rush it and it's going
to right then this is going to go really
there's a was that a camera or was that
a guard
all right that was most definitely a
camera then Cy's going to lock pick over
here and then afterward will move right
in drop that bag and then move to
restricted area or actually the cell
block we finish the restricted
area so all we got to do now is clear a
few guards and C you need to do me a
favor and not get caught
which right then in that case you go
up just go in it's not that complicated
cyber really it really is
them looping Camas that situation though
really anyways we'll get in here and
cyber is opening c
c of course anyways let's see if it's
actually
CC it is literally actually CC we'll go
meet Rose then and then afterwards we'll
move right on to the commander area to
intergate Commander to actually get rose
out of here I mean that's kind of how
this
works no s I refuse to open CI on my own
I should not let you do that next time
anyways Rose is going to take an
incredibly long more time to walk all
the way up
here it's just
waiting it's literally just waiting get
in there let's go
I technically have the slightly faster
route compar to cyber so run right past
here open up this door and then start
running up and then afterwards we'll go
to the commander area I
mean it's just a there we go get that
open move right in and that is not a
commander anyone that's actually the
commander no there it
is why are you going there of all places
there really right then we can try
something you look at
me perfect actually no
look hold on you look at
me and now
you walk all the way over here and now
cyber because you're out of radios I'm
going to answer this one
put your hands up get down un oner the
radio and cyber's going to interrogate a
commander afterwards and I'm going to
try and find what a terminal is because
that's kind of how this works so we on
to the radio and we'll get right out of
there and I trust that cyber knows how
to manage
that this is not the terminal I'm not
actually surprised by that but might as
well check I mean there is a chance that
is a lock door I'm not even going to
bother trying it I mean I could I just
don't want to I have to Lo thata
anyways I mean there's a camera here too
but it's a key card so it's going to be
there isn't it the terminal is literally
going to be there watch we're going to
have to Loop this camera and it's going
to be annoying so we Loop the camera and
then afterwards we're going to open up
this door I mean there's still one more
spot it could be and it's downstairs
somewhere
but we'll
see of course it is in front of a camera
to that's literally the worst part which
I mean I guess it does make no scram
look kind of more infuriating I mean
we've got a key card and we can't even
use it anyways all we got to do now is
get out of there hi that God I mean we
could clear the entire terminal
Commander area of gods but we don't have
to they'll
survive let's bring a commander with
us now Rose all you got to do is get up
here in a decent amount of time and then
we
can cyber I don't think you're going to
be shooting through that door any
day
really really
cyber and our bullet holes are floating
the air anyways let's get out of
here and that's the daily challenge just
under 8 minutes and 10 seconds cheers
everyone have a great time
[Music]
oh